$General	General
$Spells	Spells

$Instant	Instant
$Cast Time	Cast Time
$Magicka Cost	Magicka Cost
$Overcharge	Overcharge

$Manual	Manual
$On Key Release	On Key Release
$Automatic	Automatic
$Disabled	Disabled
$Disk	Disk
$Console	Console
$Notification	Notification
$Message Box	Message Box

$Mod Enabled	Mod Enabled
$WMAG_PENDINGACTIVATE	[Pending Activation]
$WMAG_MODACTIVATEMESSAGE	Exit all menus to allow the mod to start.
$WMAG_DISABLEMODINFO	Disable all functions of the mod. Warning, this also reset all casting related settings.
$WMAG_ENABLEMODINFO	Enable all functions of the mod.

$WMAG_LOGLEVEL	Debug Log Level
$WMAG_LOGLEVEL_INFO	Set log level, setting this to 'Disabled' disables all debug related logging. Info, Warning and Errors will still be displayed and/or logged.

$WMAG_LAT	Latency
$WMAG_LAT_INFO	The average time it takes to process spells from the time a button press is registered until spell is ready for casting (and how much time is spent after charging to prepare sounds/shaders). Click to reset averages.

$WMAG_SKIPNONESSENTIALS	Enable High Latency Detection
$WMAG_SKIPNONESSENTIALS_INFO	Enable detection of high latency (200ms+) which will disable non-essentials like shaders and sounds connected with charging and releasing spells until latency improves. (This option can degrade your immersion in favor of performance.)

$WMAG_DISCHARGEANIM	Disable Charge Animation
$WMAG_DISCHARGEANIM_INFO	Disable charging animation allowing you to move while charging a spell.

$WMAG_CONCCASTFIX	Concentration Casting Fix
$WMAG_CONCCASTFIX_INFO	Enable a fix for concentration spells getting interrupted prematurely. (Mods calling [Cast - Spell] or [DispelSpell - Actor] can cause this)

$WMAG_CHARGEMAX	Overcharge Max
$WMAG_CHARGEMAX_INFO	When Casting mode is set to Overcharge, this slider determines the maximum amount of overcharge possible. 

$WMAG_DUREXTMAX	Duration Extension Max
$WMAG_DUREXTMAX_INFO	Recasting a spell on yourself extends it's duration up to selected a maximum of selected value times the spell's original duration. Set to 0 to disable this feature.

$WMAG_DISPKEYMOD	Dispel Key Modifier
$WMAG_DISPKEYMOD_INFO	Hold this key in conjunction with a keybinding to dispel that keybound spell.

$WMAG_JUMPATTACK	Enable Jump Attack
$WMAG_JUMPATTACK_INFO	Enable the ability to attack while jumping. (This is an experimental hack)

$WMAG_SWEEPATTACK	Enable Sweeping Attacks /w 1H
$WMAG_SWEEPATTACK_INFO	Allow sweeping attacks with 1H weapons. (Disabled in towns)

$Offensive Casting	Offensive Casting

$WMAG_CHARGEMODE	Charge Mode
$WMAG_CHARGEMODE_INFO	Set the behaviour of spell queue charging. Instant (1), based on the spell's Cast Time (2), on the spell's Magicka Cost (3) relative to your maximum magicka or (4) Overcharge which allows you to charge the spell longer than it's original cast time to increase it's magnitude at the cost of more magicka.

$WMAG_MINCHARGETIME	Min. Charge Time
$WMAG_MINCHARGETIME_INFO	Set the minimum charge time in seconds, spells will never charge faster than this value.

$WMAG_MAXCHARGETIME	Max. Charge Time
$WMAG_MAXCHARGETIME_INFO	Set the minimum charge time in seconds, spells will never charge faster than this value.

$WMAG_RELEASEMODE	Release Mode
$WMAG_RELEASEMODE_INFO	Set the behaviour of spell release after charging: Manual (on attack or block), after releasing charge key (2), or automatically once charged (3)

$Defensive Casting	Defensive Casting

$WMAG_KEY	KEY
$WMAG_KEY_INFO	Click to change keybinding, set default to clear keybinding and all spells.

$WMAG_SPELL	SPELL
$WMAG_SPELL_INFO	Click to change keybound spell, set default to remove spell.

$WMAG_CHARGEOVERRIDE	Charge Override
$WMAG_CHARGEOVERRIDE_INFO	Set a charge mode override for this specific keybinding, set default to remove override.

$WMAG_RELEASEOVERRIDE	Release Override
$WMAG_RELEASEOVERRIDE_INFO	Set a release mode override for this specific keybinding, set default to remove override.

$Create a spell keybind	Create a spell keybind

$WMAG_ENABLEOVERRIDE	Enable Override
$WMAG_ENABLEOVERRIDE_INFO	Enable charge/release override setting for this keybind.

$WMAG_BINDCREATE	Click to bind key
$WMAG_BINDCREATE_INFO	Enter an unbound key to create a new keybinding or an existing key to add another spell to that key.

$WMAG_REFRESHSPELLCACHE	[Refresh spell cache]

$WMAG_KEYBINDBLOCKEDBYCACHEREFRESH	Warrior Magic is updating the spell cache, please wait before creating any keybindings..

$WMAG_UPDATINGSPELLCACHE	Currently in the process of updating spell cache, please wait..

$WMAG_UPDATESPELLCACHE	If you've recently learned some new spells and they're not showing up, you can try refreshing the spell cache. This operation can take up to a minute or more depending on how many spells your character knows but you CAN close the MCM while it runs, a notification will be displayed once it's done.
$Refresh	Refresh
$Abort	Abort

$WMAG_LOADTIMEOUT	Loading spells timed out.. If you have a lot of spells, abilities etc. it can take a while to filter, wait a little and try again.

$WMAG_UPDATINGMENU	Updating menu..

$WMAG_SPELLCACHEREFRESHED	Spell cache refreshed!
$WMAG_SPELLCACHEREFRESHING	Refreshing spell cache...

$WMAG_AUTONOMOUSCHARGING	Autonomous Charging
$WMAG_AUTONOMOUSCHARGING_INFO	Enable this if you want to charge spells without having to hold the hotkey. Charging can be canceled by pressing the hotkey again before the spell is charged.